*********************************
The Legend of Zelda - Black Crown

CREDITS
*********************************
This is a free, non-commercial, fan game.
All credits and copyright goes to their respective holders.
Feel free to read the source code and reuse it your own projects.

In unordered order

**** Companies ****
- Special thanks to Nintendo for The Legend of Zelda.
- Special thanks to Gravity Interactive Inc for Ragnarok Online.
- Special thanks to Blizzard Entertainment for Diablo.


**** Testers ****
Without you the game wouldn't be what it is today.

- kane]deth[
- Kevin
- Samuel
- Selena
- Echonia
- Marnon


**** Spriters ****
I'd like to thank all of you for your awesome spriting|ripping work.

- Oldskoolmario     for creating the Young Link sheet.
- GreenYoshiJosh    for the green hair in the Young Link sheet.
- TRM               for creating many sprites; including the deku shield.
- Rogultgot         for ripping the original OOT Link.
- Fox               for editing the original OOT Link.
- Chaotic Death     for ripping the MC vathi boss.
- Yue               for creating the MC-style Naryu and Evil Naryu.
- Jelleye           for creating the MC-style Stalchild.
- Whispy            for ripping the MC snake.
- Bacon / Kazeno    for ripping/creating the Goron.
- Chaotic Death     for the spinning Triforce.
- The Chaindog      for the MM masks.
- Kevin-1990        for the Prison tiles.
- Majora


**** Music ****
- Dan-O, thank you for offering royalty free/Creative Commons music at http://www.danosongs.com/.

- Sungha Jung, thanks for your great guitar play. We all <3 you! http://www.sunghajung.com/

- Karl Wolf and Lukas Lauermann
    Der Großbauer, music from the Gothic II mod Trail of Darkness
    http://tod.worldofgothic.de/hp/downloads.php?release_id=10

- Jesse Cook, your music is heart warming.

- Kai Rosenkranz
    Thanks for your great music. All that read this should play the Gothic series and enjoy his music.
    http://www.gog.com/en/gamecard/gothic_2_gold_edition

- xxxchobitsxxxnl, thank you so much for your nice piano solos!
    http://xxxchobitsxxxnl.wordpress.com/


**** Libraries ****
- Cygon's WIX XNA Installer - Thanks for creating an awesome installer for XNA games. (http://www.codeplex.com/xnainstaller)
- Firelight Technologies' FMOD Audio Engine (http://www.fmod.org/)
- Microsoft XNA (XNA's Not Acronymed)


**** Others ****
- HelpTheWretched - Thanks for providing fan-game creators with
  all the Zelda sounds they will need!(http://noproblo.dayjo.org/ZeldaSounds/)
- The Zelda Fan Game Central Community (http://www.zfgc.com/)
- and all the others that I have forgotten here, I am really sorry. :(
